# LINH DUONG

# **UXUI & GRAPHIC DESIGNER**

6425 Westheimer, Texas 77057 • delinh2003@yahoo.com • (808) 343 - 8917 • http://linhduong-portfolio.com

## **ABOUT ME**

UI/UX and graphic designer specialized in website & mobile app designs for Android & IOS, branding and creative illustration. Thinking out of the box, hard work, attention to detail & respect to clients are my principles. I work comfortably as both a team player and an individual designer.

## **EDUCATION**

## Graphic Design, A.A.

Brigham Young University Hawaii Class of 2013

English Language Teacher Education B.A., Fast-track Program, Distinction Vietnam National University Class of 2008

# **SPECIALTIES**

- UXUI Design
- Identity and Branding
- Email Campaign and Advertising
- Graphic, Interactive, and Print collateral
- English Vietnamese Interpretation
- Teaching English as a Foreign Language

## SKILL PROFICIENCY

Photoshop, Illustrator, In Design
Axure RP, Visio, Balsamiq
Microsoft Words, Power Point, Prezi
Written & Verbal Communication
Wordpress, Wix & other CMS
Vector Iconography & Logo
Original Illlustration
Responsive Design/e-Commerce
HTML, CSS, DreamWeaver, Frontpage

# **VOLUNTEER & MEMBER**

- AIGA active member
- Former Vice President and graphic designer at Vietnamese Chapter, Brigham Young University
- Voluntary illustrator for Vietnam Human Milk Bank and IOS app BabyMe

## **EMPLOYMENT**

## **UXUI & Graphic Designer**

Freelance - Virginia & Houston, Texas March 2014 – Present

- Create trendy website & app prototypes with great user experience, from low to high fidelity for clients in varied fields such as business, education, training, beauty & food industry, to name a few.
- Successfully create brand identity for clients of various industries including corporate business, beauty, health care, education, farming, etc.
- Design original illustrations & build versatile HTML email campaigns for clients across countries
- Engage in social impact projects to improve the good of the society

## Graphic Designer & Email Specialist

Media Prowler - Reston, Virginia October 2013 - March 2014

- Created mockups and built commercial emails campaigns for well-known clients: Audi, Ford Motor, Giant Supermarket, CVS Pharmacy, Zagat, and so on.
- Tested & deployed emails to hundreds of thousand addresses using professional deploying system.

#### **Graphic Designer**

Polynesian Cultural Center - Laie, Hawaii December 2011-August 2013

- Designed brochures, newsletters and launched various branding campaigns for US' biggest native cultural center in the Oahu island.
- Conducted surveys and participated in customer service department to study customers experience.

#### Interpreter/Translator

Freelance - Vietnam & Honolulu, Hawaii January 2006 - October 2010

- Volunteer interpreter/administrator at APEC United States, Honolulu HI, USA November 2009
- Data Quality Audit of a Malaria Grant supported by the Global Fund, GFA Consulting Group, Sep 2009
- Liaison officer for 13th ASEAN University Games, accompanying Chief Officer of Vietnam delegations.

#### **English Lecturer**

Vietnam National University, Hanoi Vietnam June 2008 - September 2009

• Taught English to junior and senior Vietnamese students & participated in making national tests